# ARTUR SHAMSUTDINOV

# FLUTTER DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

+7 927 932 40 82

 $\bowtie$ 

a.shamsutdinov@icloud.com

57

github.com/roketstorm



linkedin.com/in/roketstorm

SKILLS

Dart/Flutter

Ruby/Ruby on Rails

PHP/HTML/CSS

Linux Server Administration

-----

# EDUCATION

Bachelor of IT

# Ufa State Aviation Technical University

2010 - 2014

Russia, Ufa

Master of IT

# Ufa State Aviation Technical University

2014 - 2016

Russia, Ufa

-----

# LANGUAGES

Russian Native

English Professional / B2

Spanish Beginner / A1

### PROFILE

Hi!

My name is Artur Shamsutdinov.

I am a Mobile Developer with over 5 years of experience. I am also working on different interactive media projects, open source, websites and trying to go beyond typical use cases and be T-shaped person. I am really into photography, music and (sometimes) gamedev.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Flutter Engineer**

Surf LTD 2021 - Current

- Multiplatform mobile app development, team leading, mentorship, technical support on pre-sales stages
- The Hole (Video streaming app): technical support, part-time team leading, developing animation features, improving UX. Team of 5 people Dart, Flutter, Elementary, Animations, Swagger, Golden tests, Dio, Firebase Analytics, Firebase Crashlytics, Android, iOS
- MARS DSN (Corporate educational app): team leading, setting up release pages in App Store and Google Play, making release builds for stores. Team of 3 people - Dart, Flutter, Elementary, Firebase Analytics, Android, iOS
- Inspector Cloud (Al-based app for supermarkets): development of several features for merchants and moderators of the system, development of search feature for different lists of data, integration of image recognition with camera of device, working with local database powered by sqlite, offline mode. Team of 5 people - Dart, Flutter, Platform Channels, SQL, Sqflite, Android, iOS
- Gosuslugi.DOM (House management app): revision of app architecture, added MWWM pattern, revision of app navigation system, development of real-time chat, working with native file system and camera. Team of 5 people - Dart, Flutter, Elementary, BLoC, Streams, Dio, iOS, Android
- Onyxia: Cybersecurity Intel (News app): design of app architecture, team leading, markup and MVP development in short period of time (1 month), setting up and releasing builds in mobile apps stores, integration of multi-level navigation, deep linking, push notifications setup, drawing custom charts. Team of 3 people Dart, Flutter, Elementary, Provider, Push-notifications, auto\_route, Firebase Cloud Messaging, Firebase Analytics, Dio, Retrofit, iOS, Android

# **Full Stack Mobile Engineer**

MEGI MC 2017 - 2021

- Multiplatform mobile and desktop app development, backend development, mentorship
- MEGI&Farmlend (Healthcare app for clients of medical centers): design of app architecture and app features, rewriting from Cordova and React Native to Flutter, integration with e-commerce, pharmacies, working with maps, setting up and releasing in AppStore and Google Play. Team of 1, expanded to 2 people on the final stages of the project - Dart, Flutter, Provider, Google Maps, Dio, Cordova, JavaScript, React Native, Xamarin

# ARTUR SHAMSUTDINOV

# FLUTTER DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

+79

+7 927 932 40 82

 $\bowtie$ 

a.shamsutdinov@icloud.com



github.com/roketstorm



linkedin.com/in/roketstorm

#### COURSES

- Learning Google Flutter for Mobile Developers - LinkedIn Learning
- Dart Advanced Course Udemy
- Introduction to Xamarin.iOS LinkedIn Learning
- Learning Google Firebase for Flutter
   LinkedIn Learning
- UX Design for Developers LinkedIn Learning
- Clean Code with Dart LinkedIn Learning
- Interaction Design: Software and Web Design Patterns - LinkedIn Learning
- LFCS: Linux Service Management -Pluralsight
- Intensive 20 A1 Españolé International House Valencia-Spanish School
- Get Started with iOS App
  Development LinkedIn Learning

# ACHIEVEMENTS

- Awardee of regional competition «KRIT-2010» - «Game programming»
- Winner of regional competition «KRIT-2008» - «New word in programming»
- Multiple participation in "LudumDare" rapid game development contest
- Awardee of competition for students and graduates of Higher School of Economics in 2014 in section "Journalism Media production in creative industries."
- 4th place in Flutter Flame Game Jam 2022

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Full Stack Mobile Engineer**

MEGI MC

2017 - 2021

- Backend: development of internal web-services and WebAPIs for mobile and desktop apps on Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, C#, .NET Core on Linux machines, Microsoft SQL Server
- Other: development of desktop Windows app on Flutter for electronic queues, working with QR-Code scanners and printers. Team of 2 people - Dart, Flutter, dart:ffi, Win32 API

# Web Developer

Webprostranstvo LLC

2016 - 2017

- · Website development on 1C-Bitrix CMS
- Teaching clients on how to manage their websites
- · Technical support on pre-sales stages
- Mobile app development on Cordova and Angular
- Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Cordova, MySQL, Wordpress, 1C-Bitrix, CentOS

### **Web Developer**

**GK Soft-Service LLC** 

2015 - 2016

- Website development on 1C-Bitrix CMS
- Teaching clients on how to manage their websites
- · Technical support on pre-sales stages
- Mobile app development on Cordova
- Tech Stack: PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Cordova, MySQL, 1C-Bitrix

# **Ruby Developer Intern**

**Hungry Sites** 

June 2011 - August 2011

- Website markup with HTML and CSS
- Learning Ruby programing language
- Learning Ruby on Rails framework
- · Learning Git
- Learning Locomotive CMS